JOI, jerk-off instruction. During this presentation, we will be discussing JOI, which
is short for jerk-off instruction. Definition:
Jerk-off instruction is verbal and sometimes visual prompts about how a man should
masturbate and when to orgasm, if at all.
Jerk-off instruction is often a component of orgasm denial as practiced by clients
in the BDSM community. However, it can also be an element of foreplay for vanilla
clients looking for a girlfriend experience.
Jerk-off instruction is often shortened to JOI.
Jerk-off instruction tends to be a dominant activity as it involves taking control
and instructing. However, this does not mean the clients always want to be humiliated.
There are two main types of JOI. Jerk-off encouragement Positive
reinforcement to help a client orgasm. Often paired with the girlfriend's experience.
Do not humiliate them. Offer kindness, comfort and escape from their life.
Play the long-distance girlfriend who misses them.
Look to connect with and embrace them. Jerk-off humiliation.
Plays on submissive fetishes. Make the client feel dirty and ashamed of his arousal
and need to masturbate. Can be combined with lots of other dominant activities.
Always check before you start your session to establish the limits of your client.
Don't be afraid to find out exactly what they want so you can adapt the session to
meet their personality. There is nothing wrong with asking a few questions.
They are likely to appreciate you taking the time to get to know them.
Some questions to ask to establish their desires.
It's good to ask questions to establish your client's desires and find out what they
enjoy. Do you enjoy small penis humiliation?
Small penis humiliation is where you laugh and make jokes about the size of their
penis. We go into this in more detail on another presentation.
CEI. Come eating instructions. CEI is where you make them eat their own cum
and tell them when and how to do it. Edging.
Edging is where you bring them to the edge of cumming and then force them to stop.
You can do this over and over again and these type of chats usually take a larger
amount of time to perform. Humiliation. What kind?
We discuss all different types of humiliation later on in the course.
G.F.E. Girlfriend experience. The girlfriend experience is perfect for the less dominant
clients. You act like their significant other and take an active interest in them
and their wellbeing, encouraging them to relax and letting you take care of them
and their sexual desires. The performance.
Be confident. Don't ask, just tell them. This is why it's important to establish
limits before so you know how far you can push them.
The client wants to feel like you are in full control of them.
They want to be told what to do. Sit tall and be 100% sure in what you're telling
them. This is going to drive them wild. Be in control.
Being in control works with both types of JOI.
Tell them exactly what you want them to do.
Tell them what to touch and what not to touch, how fast to go, how slow to go.
Tell them to go fast and then demand they let go and sit on their hands.
Giggle and say well done and then tell them to continue.
Tell them to grab their balls or hit their balls.
This can be adjusted depending on their likes or dislikes.
Put your own twist on it. Come countdown.
Submissive clients love a come countdown.
They are not allowed to come until you reach number one.
Begin at ten and go as slow or as fast as you like.
The goal is for them to climax at one. Remember that you can always stop at any number
and then go back up to ten and start the whole process again.
You want them to be begging you to come. Tease and talk.
Use your body to tease but don't give too much away.
You can do a little strip but not let them touch themselves at all.
Most of the talking should be instructing them what to do but if they have mentioned
they like other things it's a good idea to bring this in.
You can also tell them that they need to be taught to touch themselves correctly
and how not to come quickly. Hi everyone we hope that these tips are helpful to you
and you're able to use them on cam and we would also recommend that you don't rush
you really take your time. A lot of clients that enjoy JOI enjoy the build up to
the climax so you can really use this to your advantage and keep them in your chat
room for longer which is the main goal here.
You can also trick them when doing the come countdown and when you're counting down
from ten to one you can stop wherever you like on whatever number and have it start
again. This way obviously it's keeping them in there for longer so and they're going
to enjoy it too so it's good for both of you.
Some clients enjoy tipping and some don't so if your particular client doesn't seem
too keen on that then I wouldn't push him and also be creative with this you
know really just mix things up try different things and if you find something that
works really well for you write it down and then you can try it again with the same
client or with a different client in the future.
And finally good luck I'm excited to see how everyone gets on with this.
Thank you girlies, see you soon.